Historical Audiovisual Collection, 1912-2012 (bulk 1945-1996 ): Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 3: Campus Life, 1945-2009; 276 items
  - Athletics, 1919-2010; 167 items
    - Football - Tigers Mangle Yale Ivy Hopes, 2009; 57; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 196)
      Newsreel covering the Princeton-Yale football game at Palmer Stadium, in which Princeton beat Yale 13-0, preventing Yale's Ivy League championship. Watching the game are Robert B. Meyner, governor of New Jersey, and Margaret Truman, daughter of the former president. The game is preceded by footage of visitors picnicking outside the stadium.. Created by Colorlab. Digital Betacam; Duration: 3:24.
    - Football - Tigers Mangle Yale Ivy Hopes, 2009; 57; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 217)
      Newsreel covering the Princeton-Yale football game at Palmer Stadium, in which Princeton beat Yale 13-0, preventing Yale's Ivy League championship. Watching the game are Robert B. Meyner, governor of New Jersey, and Margaret Truman, daughter of the former president. The game is preceded by footage of visitors picnicking outside the stadium. DVCAM or MiniDV; Duration: 3:24.
    - Football Princeton-Harvard, 2009; 166; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 196)
      Annotated silent movie of the football match between Harvard and Princeton at Princeton's Palmer Stadium. The game ended in a 10-10 tie.. Created by Colorlab. Digital Betacam; Duration: 25:15.
    - Football Princeton-Harvard, 2009; 166; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 223)
      Annotated silent movie of the football match between Harvard and Princeton at Princeton's Palmer Stadium. The game ended in a 10-10 tie.. Created by Colorlab. MPEG-2; Duration: 25:15.
    - Football Princeton-Harvard, 2009; 166; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 223)
      Annotated silent movie of the football match between Harvard and Princeton at Princeton's Palmer Stadium. The game ended in a 10-10 tie.. Created by Colorlab. MPEG-4; Duration: 25:15.
    - "Princeton Football, the Winning Way", 2009; 218; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 196)
      Recruiting video, including interviews with players and coaching staff, and footage of training sessions and games at Palmer Stadium.. Created by Colorlab. Digital Betacam.
    - "Princeton Football, the Winning Way", 2009; 218; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 223)
      Recruiting video, including interviews with players and coaching staff, and footage of training sessions and games at Palmer Stadium.. Created by Colorlab. MPEG-2.
    - "Princeton Football, the Winning Way", 2009; 218; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 223)
      Recruiting video, including interviews with players and coaching staff, and footage of training sessions and games at Palmer Stadium.. Created by Colorlab. MPEG-4.
    - Diving practice, circa 2009; 65; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 134)
      Outdoor jumping practice scenes on campus (in color) alternatived with black and white swimming pool jumping scenes. 16 mm; Duration: 4:30.
    - Diving practice, circa 2009; 65; 1 Disc(s) (Box 226)
      Outdoor jumping practice scenes on campus (in color) alternatived with black and white swimming pool jumping scenes. Created by Princeton Media Services. DVD; Duration: 4:30.
    - Football - Tigers Mangle Yale Ivy Hopes, 2010; 57; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 222)
      Newsreel covering the Princeton-Yale football game at Palmer Stadium, in which Princeton beat Yale 13-0, preventing Yale's Ivy League championship. Watching the game are Robert B. Meyner, governor of New Jersey, and Margaret Truman, daughter of the former president. The game is preceded by footage of visitors picnicking outside the stadium.. Created by Colorlab. MPEG-2; Duration: 3:24.
    - Football - Tigers Mangle Yale Ivy Hopes, 2010; 57; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 222)
      Newsreel covering the Princeton-Yale football game at Palmer Stadium, in which Princeton beat Yale 13-0, preventing Yale's Ivy League championship. Watching the game are Robert B. Meyner, governor of New Jersey, and Margaret Truman, daughter of the former president. The game is preceded by footage of visitors picnicking outside the stadium.. Created by Colorlab. MPEG-4; Duration: 3:24.
    - Lacrosse, undated; 90; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 142)
    - Football - Princeton vs. Penn, undated; 146; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 156)
      Franklin Field. 16 mm.
    - Football - Princeton vs. Yale, undated; 149; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 156)
    - Football - Princeton "Sideline" Football, undated; 151; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 156)
    - Football - Princeton vs. Yale, undated; 152; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 156)
    - Football - highlights, undated; 153; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 156)
    - Football, undated; 154; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 159)
    - Football - 1940s or 1950s, undated; 155; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 159)
    - Football - Princeton vs. Navy, undated; 168; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 161)
    - Gymnastics, undated; 177; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 159)
    - Baseball, undated; 179; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 159)
    - Baseball, undated; 179; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 225)
    - Polo, undated; 182; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 164)
    - Princeton - Yale Football, undated; AR.2005.105; 2291; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 216)
  - War/Military, 1945-2009; 45 items
    Subseries contains materials related to war-time activities and events.
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Bill Douglas, 239; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 52)
      Created by Class of 1945. Compact cassette.
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Jett McCormick, 240; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 52)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Stewart Carothers, 241; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 52)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Gerald McConney, 242; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 52)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - John Moulinier, 243; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 52)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Boggs (Lawrence S.) Lewis, 244; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 52)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Bruce Silver, 245; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 52)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Steve Palmer, 246; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 52)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - F.I.G. Coleman, 247; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 52)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Don Lambert, 248; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 52)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Jim Calvert, 249; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 52)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Howard Wells, 250; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 52)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Bill Gallagher and James Mills, 251; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 52)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - George Bonsall, 252; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 52)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Ted Crane, 253; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 52)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - William Campbell, 254; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 53)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - John Abbott, 255; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 53)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Bob Peers, 256; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 53)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - William Peck, 257; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 53)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Jim Wright, 258; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 53)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Harvey Kelsey, 259; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 53)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Chet Files, 260; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 53)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Stew (Harris B.) Stewart, 261; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 53)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - John Watkins, 262; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 53)
      Korean War. Created by Class of 1945. Compact cassette.
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Stan Root, 263; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 53)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - John Mosser, 264; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 53)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Ed Simsarian, 265; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 53)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Tom Horn, 266; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 53)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Dick Nash, 267; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 53)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Charles Reeves, 268; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 53)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - George Dexter, 269; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 54)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Will Spencer, 270; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 54)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - C.R. Brewer, 271; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 54)
    - Class of 1945 World War II Oral History Project - Dave Spencer, 272; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 54)
    - Eisenhower -- National Convention of American Legion, 1954; 648; 2 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 60)
    - ROTC, 1961; 134; 2 Film Reel(s) (Box 134)
    - Vietnam Teach-In, 1969; AR.2010.149; 2354; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 225)
      This recording documents the October 1969 Vietnam War Teach-In at the Dillon Gyn at Princeton University. Master. Created by WPRB. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
    - Vietnam Teach-In, 1970; AR.2010.149; 2354; 4 Disc(s) (Box 225)
      This recording documents the October 1969 Vietnam War Teach-In at the Dillon Gyn at Princeton University. Copies. Compact disc.
    - Marching Scenes on Campus, 2009; 106; 1 Videocassette(s) (Box 196)
      From the Princeton University Archives: Groups of various military service units marching on campus. Princeton University housed many different training schools during WWII, including the Army Specialized Training Program (A-12) and the Navy and Marine Corps (V-12).. Created by Colorlab. Digital Betacam; Duration: 2:45.
    - Marching Scenes on Campus, 2009; 106; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 223)
      From the Princeton University Archives: Groups of various military service units marching on campus. Princeton University housed many different training schools during WWII, including the Army Specialized Training Program (A-12) and the Navy and Marine Corps (V-12).. Created by Colorlab. MPEG-2; Duration: 2:45.
    - Marching Scenes on Campus, 2009; 106; 1 Digital File(s) (Box 223)
      From the Princeton University Archives: Groups of various military service units marching on campus. Princeton University housed many different training schools during WWII, including the Army Specialized Training Program (A-12) and the Navy and Marine Corps (V-12).. Created by Colorlab. MPEG-4; Duration: 2:45.
    - Marching Scenes on Campus, undated; 106; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 134)
      From the Princeton University Archives: Groups of various military service units marching on campus. Princeton University housed many different training schools during WWII, including the Army Specialized Training Program (A-12) and the Navy and Marine Corps (V-12). 16 mm; Duration: 2:45.
    - British War Film--WWII, undated; 107; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 147)
      presented to Alexander Leitch by the R.A.F. during a British week-end course. Created by R.A.F. 16 mm.
    - ROTC, undated; 184; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 164)
    - ROTC, undated; 185; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 164)
- Series 4: Events, 1912-2013; 472 items
  The Events series contains audiovisual materials pertaining to events held on campus, to include celebrations/dedications, theatrical performances, and conferences. Series also contains newsreels and documentary materials related to campus events. The Events series is arranged into five subseries: Conferences/meetings, Celebrations/Dedications, Documentary/Newsreels, Judicial hearings, and Theater.
  - Conferences/Meetings, 1954-2007; 69 items
    - Adlai Stevenson -- PA State Democratic Party Banquet, 1954; 659; 2 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 60)
      WCAU 9pm. 33 1/3 rpm album.
    - $53 Million for Princeton University -- 5th and Final Broadcast Meeting, 1961; 698; 1 Phonograph Record(s) (Box 60)
      33 1/3 rpm album; Duration: 50 min.
    - Special Committee on Sponsored Research, 1970; 591; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 79)
    - Special Committee on Sponsored Research, 1970; 606; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 80)
    - Special Committee on Sponsored Research, 1970; 607; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 80)
    - Special Committee on Sponsored Research, 1970; 608; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 80)
    - Special Committee on Sponsored Research, 1970; 609; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 80)
    - Strike Assembly Discussion, 1970; 743; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 82)
    - Strike Assembly Discussion, 1970; 743; 2 Disc(s) (Box 224)
      Compact disc.
    - Strike Assembly Discussion, 1970; 743; 1 Disc(s) (Box 224)
      2nd copy of disc/reel 1 only. Compact disc.
    - 1970 Princeton Strike - Cambodia Assembly, 1586; 1 Disc(s) (Box 204)
    - 1970 Princeton Strike - Cambodia Assembly, 1586; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 104)
    - 1970 Princeton Strike - Cambodia Assembly, 1586; 1 Disc(s) (Box 224)
    - 1970 Princeton Strike - "4/30/1970, Track 2", 1591; 1 Disc(s) (Box 204)
    - 1970 Princeton Strike - "4/30/1970, Track 2", 1591; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 104)
    - 1970 Princeton Strike - "4/30/1970, Track 2", 1591; 1 Disc(s) (Box 224)
    - 1970 Princeton Strike - meeting at Jadwin, 1592; 1 Disc(s) (Box 204)
      Audio recording of WPRB Radio, reporting live from Jadwin Gym on May 4, 1970, with accompanying photos. Following the American invasion in Cambodia on April 30, 1970, some 3,500 students, faculty and staff assembled on May 4 in Jadwin Gym to vote on a "strike against the war." Three proposals were discussed, and the first, submitted by the Council of the Princeton University Community (CPUC), which included a statement of opposition to the war and the recommendation to suspend final exams, won with a majority of 2,066 votes. Compact disc.
    - 1970 Princeton Strike - meeting at Jadwin, 1592; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 104)
      Audio recording of WPRB Radio, reporting live from Jadwin Gym on May 4, 1970, with accompanying photos. Following the American invasion in Cambodia on April 30, 1970, some 3,500 students, faculty and staff assembled on May 4 in Jadwin Gym to vote on a "strike against the war." Three proposals were discussed, and the first, submitted by the Council of the Princeton University Community (CPUC), which included a statement of opposition to the war and the recommendation to suspend final exams, won with a majority of 2,066 votes. Compact cassette.
    - 1970 Princeton Strike - meeting at Jadwin, Digital Files: 1
      Item number: 1592. Audio recording of WPRB Radio, reporting live from Jadwin Gym on May 4, 1970, with accompanying photos. Following the American invasion in Cambodia on April 30, 1970, some 3,500 students, faculty and staff assembled on May 4 in Jadwin Gym to vote on a "strike against the war." Three proposals were discussed, and the first, submitted by the Council of the Princeton University Community (CPUC), which included a statement of opposition to the war and the recommendation to suspend final exams, won with a majority of 2,066 votes.
    - 1970 Princeton Strike - meeting at Dillon Gymnasium, 1593; 1 Disc(s) (Box 204)
    - 1970 Princeton Strike - meeting at Dillon Gymnasium, 1593; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 104)
    - 1970 Princeton Strike - University meeting, 1594; 1 Disc(s) (Box 204)
    - 1970 Princeton Strike - University meeting, 1594; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 104)
    - 1970 Princeton Strike - Institute for Defense Analysis (IDA) incidents, 1595; 1 Disc(s) (Box 204)
    - 1970 Princeton Strike - Institute for Defense Analysis (IDA) incidents, 1595; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 104)
    - Faculty Meeting, 1970; 1792; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 109)
    - Meeting at Dillon Gymnasium, 1970; 1793; 1 Disc(s) (Box 204)
    - Meeting at Dillon Gymnasium, 1970; 1793; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 109)
    - 1970 Strike - Meeting at Jadwin, 1794; 2 Disc(s) (Box 204)
    - 1970 Strike - Meeting at Jadwin, 1794; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 109)
    - Meeting at Jadwin, Faculty Meeting, 1970; 1795; 1 Disc(s) (Box 204)
    - Meeting at Jadwin, Faculty Meeting, 1970; 1795; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 109)
    - Meeting at Jadwin, Faculty Meeting, 1970; 1795; 1 Disc(s) (Box 224)
      Disc 1 of 2. Compact disc.
    - Faculty Meeting, 1970; 1796; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 109)
    - Faculty Meeting, 1970; 1797; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 109)
    - Faculty Meeting, 1970; 1798; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 110)
    - Faculty Meeting, 1970; 1799; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 110)
    - University Meeting, 1970; 1800; 1 Disc(s) (Box 204)
    - University Meeting, 1970; 1800; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 110)
    - 1970 strike - unidentified meeting, 2336; 1 Disc(s) (Box 224)
      This is a duplicate of an unidentified recording probably already in the collection. Disc 2 of 2. Compact disc; Duration: 11:40.
    - 1970 strike - unidentified meeting, 2337; 1 Disc(s) (Box 224)
      This is a duplicate of an unidentified recording probably already in the collection. Disc 2 of 2; 2 copies. Compact disc; Duration: 20:32.
    - 1970 strike - unidentified meeting, 2338; 2 Disc(s) (Box 224)
      This is a duplicate of an unidentified recording probably already in the collection. Disc 2 of 2; 2 copies. Compact disc.
    - Unidentified man with light British accent giving speech about womens' liberation and the American left, possibly part of 1970 strike, 2339; 1 Disc(s) (Box 224)
      This is a duplicate of an unidentified recording probably already in the collection. Disc 2 of 2. Compact disc; Duration: approximately 40 minutes.
    - 1970 strike - faculty meeting, 2340; 2 Disc(s) (Box 224)
    - 1970 strike - faculty meeting, 2341; 1 Disc(s) (Box 224)
      This is a duplicate of an unidentified recording probably already in the collection. Disc 2 of 2. Compact disc.
    - 1970 strike - faculty meeting, 2342; 2 Disc(s) (Box 224)
    - 1970 strike - faculty meeting, 2343; 1 Disc(s) (Box 224)
      This is a duplicate of an unidentified recording probably already in the collection. Disc 1 of 2. Compact disc.
    - 1970 strike - faculty meeting, 2344; 1 Disc(s) (Box 1224)
    - 1970 strike - faculty meeting, 2345; 2 Disc(s) (Box 224)
    - 1970 strike - faculty meeting, 2347; 2 Disc(s) (Box 224)
      This is a duplicate of an unidentified recording probably already in the collection. Compact disc.
    - 1970 strike - unidentified meeting, 2348; 1 Disc(s) (Box 224)
      This is a duplicate of an unidentified recording probably already in the collection. Compact disc; Duration: 11:40.
    - Special Committee on Sponsored Research, 1971; 610; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 80)
    - Special Committee on Sponsored Research, 1971; 611; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 80)
    - Special Program on President-Elect Bowen including press conference at which his election was announced, 1971; 2120; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 210)
      Broadcast on 12/2/71 at 7pm, produced by WPRB News. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
    - Princeton Town Meeting?, 1972; 1944; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 114)
    - President Robert Goheen Statement at Princeton University Chapel Strike Meeting and Dean of Students Neil Rudenstine Statement, 1972; AR.2007.034; 2050; 1 Disc(s) (Box 209)
      Goheen Speech on Action to be Taken Against Disruption of Classes. Compact disc.
    - President Robert Goheen Statement at Princeton University Chapel Strike Meeting and Dean of Students Neil Rudenstine Statement, 1972; 2050; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 211)
      Goheen Speech on Action to be Taken Against Disruption of Classes. Used by Robert Allen and Greenspan to make the Goheen video (item #2025). DAT cassette.
    - Princeton 4/26/1974, 593; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 101)
    - Trustee Student Life Discussion, 1976; 2183; 1 Audio Reel(s) (Box 210)
      Corwin Hall. 1/4 inch magnetic tape, 7-inch reel.
    - Tiger Magazine -- Graduate Board Meeting, 1982; 2209; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 211)
    - Medicare Conference, 1984; 1815; 7 Audiocassette(s) (Box 110)
      Tapes are labeled #1, 6-11. Compact cassette.
    - Medicare Conference - Prospect Garden Room, 1984; 1822; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 110)
    - The Photograph and the American Indian, 1985; 1802; 13"Audiocassette(s) (Box 110)
    - The Photograph and the American Indian, 1985; 1814; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 110)
      Tape 13, Side 2. Compact cassette.
    - Program for NJ Affairs, CNJA Meeting, 1988; 1705; 2 Audiocassette(s) (Box 107)
    - Press Conference, President Shapiro, 1988; 1875; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 203)
    - Press Conference, President Shapiro, 1988; 1875; 1 Audiocassette(s) (Box 112)
    - Princeton University Faculty Meeting, 2007; 2032; 1 Disc(s) (Box 204)
    - $53 Million for Princeton University -- 5th and Final Broadcast Meeting, undated; 698; 4 Disc(s) (Box 224)
      2 copies. Compact disc; Duration: 50 min.
  - Celebrations/Dedications, 1912-2013; 144 items
    Subseries contains materials related to campus celebrations, dedications, inaugurations, and awards.
    - Class of 1928 Flour Picture and Commencement, 1912; 133; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 134)
      Previously misidentified as "Hibben Inauguration." This silent movie, which includes fragmented and repeated scenes and was probably used during a reunion, captures commencement activities of what is assumed to be the Class of 1928, including a benediction by president John Grier Hibben, the smashing of pipes at Cannon Green, and various P-rade scenes. It includes footage of the Class' freshmen "flour picture," when sophomores would dump flour and water on the freshmen prior to their first class picture on the steps of Whig Hall. The P-rade scenes include footage of a tiger and the class of 1909 with noted alumnus Harold Medina. 16 mm; Duration: 6:41.
    - John Grier Hibben's Inauguration and Woodrow Wilson voting; Commencement footage and P-rade scenes 1928, 1912; 192; 1 Film Reel(s) (Box 171)
      Silent newsreel of the inauguration of John Grier Hibben as president of Princeton University on May 11, 1912, featuring US President William Howard Taft, who received on honorary degree on the occasion, as well as Chief Justice Edward Douglass. Followed by Gaumont newsreel footage of two visits of President Woodrow Wilson to his home town to vote September 23, 1913 or September, 28, 1915 and April 25,1916. Also includes commencement activities from 1928, starting with the breaking of the pipes at Cannon Green, followed by graduation scenes of the Class of 1928, P-rade scenes, and senior singing. 16 mm.
    - John Grier Hibben's Inauguration and Woodrow Wilson voting; Commencement footage and P-rade scenes 1928, 1912; Digital Files: 1
      Item number: 192. Commencement and P-rade 1928 portion only. Silent newsreel of the inauguration of John Grier Hibben as president of Princeton University on May 11, 1912, featuring US President William Howard Taft, who received on honorary degree on the occasion, as well as Chief Justice Edward Douglass. Followed by Gaumont newsreel footage of two visits of President Woodrow Wilson to his home town to vote September 23, 1913 or September, 28, 1915 and April 25,1916. Also includes commencement activities from 1928, starting with the breaking of the pipes at Cannon Green, followed by graduation scenes of the Class of 1928, P-rade scenes, and senior singing.. Created by Princeton Media Services".
    - John Grier Hibben's Inauguration and Woodrow Wilson voting; Commencement footage and P-rade scenes 1928, 1912; Digital Files: 1